<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by PaymentOne.com-->
<!--label details for paymentone template-->
<PaymentOne country_code="US" language_code="EN">
  <Home>
    <homelabel for="How it Works?">How it Works? US EN</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Select an item:">Select an item:</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Please enter your home phone number">Please enter your home phone number</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Continue">Continue</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Remember My Number">Remember My Number</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Verifying phone number.">Verifying phone number.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Sorry, we can not bill the home phone number [phonenumber] you provided. Please try again.">Sorry, we can not bill the home phone number [phonenumber] you provided. Please try again.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Sorry, we are unable to verify the information you provided. Please try our mobile phone number option.">Sorry, we are unable to verify the information you provided. Please try our mobile phone number option.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="To complete your transaction, please provide the following details.">To complete your transaction, please provide the following details.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="First Name">First Name</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Last Name">Last Name</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Address">Address</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Zip Code">Zip Code</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Month/Year of Birth">Month/Year of Birth</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Terms of Service">Terms of Service</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Terms Content (QWEST)">Are you at least 18 years of age and authorized to make changes and incur charges to this telephone account, (BTN)?[radiooption1]

Do you understand and agree that you are giving your authorization for (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name), to bill your local phone bill in the amount of $(Amount) for this service?[radiooption2]

Although there is no affiliation between the two companies, do you understand that (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name) charge will appear in your local telephone bill on the PaymentOne bill page, billed on behalf of (Corporate Name)?" [radiooption3]

(Corporate Name) authorization to provide and bill its services is obtained by way of your electronic signature. Once submitted, this electronic order constitutes an electronic letter of agency authorized by your electronic signature. (Corporate Name) reliance on your electronic signature, as obtained herein, as done pursuant to the Uniform Electronic transactions Act ("UETA") and the Electronic Signatures in Global and National transactions Act ("E-Sign"). Both laws specifically preempt state laws that recognize only paper records or handwritten signatures.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Terms Content (NON QWEST)">You are stating that you are 18 years or older and are duly authorized by the account owner to make changes to and incur charges to the telephone number account, (BTN). You understand and agree to the purchase in the amount of $(Amount) for (Product Description) and are authorizing this charge to be placed on the telephone number provided. You are aware that although there is no affiliation with your local phone company, all charges will appear on the PaymentOne or eBillit  bill page as billed on behalf of (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name).  For customer service inquiries including cancellation, contact (Corporate name, address1, address2, city, state, zip code, toll free phone number and/or support email).

(Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name), authorization to provide and bill its services is obtained by way of your electronic signature. Once submitted, this electronic order constitutes an electronic letter of agency authorized by your electronic signature. (Corporate Name) reliance on your electronic signature, as obtained herein, as done pursuant to the Uniform Electronic transactions Act ("UETA") and the Electronic Signatures in Global and National transactions Act ("E-Sign"). Both laws specifically preempt state laws that recognize only paper records or handwritten signatures.

&lt;span style="font-weight:bold; font-size:11px;"&gt;AT&amp;T Customers:&lt;/span&gt;
You have the right to dispute the (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name), charges billed on your local telephone bill. You are not legally responsible for (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name), charges incurred by minors or vulnerable adults without your consent. Your local telephone service will not be disconnected because you fail to pay a charge by (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name), except that nonpayment of certain regulated telecommunication charges may result in disconnection of service in Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Louisiana, South Carolina and Tennessee. Enhanced Telecommunications Service Providers may employ other agencies to collect delinquent charge, even if your local phone company has previously adjusted them from your telephone bill.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="I Agree to Terms of Service">I Agree to Terms of Service</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Authorization.">Authorization.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Processing order.">Processing order.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Time remaining to call">Time remaining to call</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Purchase Confirmed">Purchase Confirmed</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Your purchase was successfully completed.">Your purchase was successfully completed.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Transaction Cancelled.">Transaction Cancelled.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Sorry, this transaction has been cancelled as you have not completed the transaction within the 10 minute time window.">We're sorry, but your transaction was not completed because the allotted time has elapsed. Please go back to the checkout page and try again.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Post Sale Disclosure Notice">Thank you for your purchase of (Product Description) for $(Amount). Although (Corporate Name), which provides (Service/Product Name), is not affiliated with your local phone company, these charges will appear on your local telephone bill on the PaymentOne or eBillit bill page as billed on behalf of (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name). You must be 18 years old and duly authorized by the telephone account owner to make changes to and incur charges on this telephone account provided. For all customer service inquires, including cancellation, contact us at (toll free phone number, support email, or Corporate Name, address1, addess2, city, state, zipcode).</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Home Phone Number">Home Phone Number</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Post Sale Disclosure Notice for AT&amp;T Customers">&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold; font-size:11px;"&gt;AT&amp;T Customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;
You have the right to dispute the (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name), charges billed on your local telephone bill. You are not legally responsible for (Service/Product Name), a service of (Corporate Name), charges incurred by minors or vulnerable adults without your consent. Your local telephone service will not be disconnected because you fail to pay a charge by  (Service/Product Name), a service of  (Corporate Name), except that nonpayment of certain regulated telecommunications charges may result in disconnection of service in Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Louisiana, South Carolina and Tennessee.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Post Sale Disclosure Notice for Qwest Customers">&lt;u&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight:bold; font-size:11px;"&gt;Qwest Customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;span style="font-weight:bold; font-size:11px;"&gt;DISCLAIMER THOSE IN QWEST TERRITORY IN STATES EXCEPT MN (WA, OR, AZ, ID, MT, WY, UT, CO ND, SD, NE, IA, NM)&lt;/span&gt;
(Product Description) CHARGES ARE CONSIDERED ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATIONS SERVICES. WHEN YOU ELECT TO BILL ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATIONS SERVICES ON YOUR QWEST TELEPHONE BILL, NEITHER YOUR LOCAL OR LONG DISTANCE SERVICE CAN BE DISCONNECTED FOR FAILURE TO PAY THESE CHARGES. ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATIONS SERVICE PROVIDERS MAY EMPLOY OTHER AGENCIES TO COLLECT DELINQUENT SERVICE CHARGES, EVEN IF QWEST HAS PREVIOUSLY ADJUSTED THEM FROM YOUR TELEPHONE BILL.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Post Sale Disclosure Notice for state of Minnesota only">&lt;span style="font-weight:bold; font-size:11px;"&gt;DISCLAIMER FOR THE STATE OF MINNESOTA ONLY&lt;/span&gt;
(Product Description) CHARGES ARE CONSIDERED ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATIONS SERVICES. YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TO DISPUTE ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATION SERVICE CHARGES BILLED ON YOUR QWEST TELEPHONE BILL. AS A TELEPHONE SERVICE SUBSCRIBER, YOU ARE NOT LEGALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATIONS SERVICE CHARGES INCURRED BY MINORS OR VULNERABLE ADULTS WITHOUT YOUR CONSENT. NEITHER A LONG DISTANCE COMPANY NOR QWEST MAY DISCONNECT YOUR LOCAL TELEPHONE OR LONG DISTANCE SERVICE BECAUSE YOU REFUSE TO PAY AN ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATIONS SERVICE CHARGE. ENHANCED TELECOMMUNICATIONS SERVICE PROVIDERS MAY EMPLOY OTHER AGENCIES TO COLLECT DELINQUENT AMOUNTS.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="I am confirming the following purchase:">I am confirming the following purchase:</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Item:">Item:</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Price:">Price:</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Billing:">Billing:</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Done">Done</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Pay with your Home Phone">Pay with your Home Phone</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Display Home Number">Home Number</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Confirm">Confirm</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="City">City</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="State">State</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Legal Disclaimer">Legal Disclaimer</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR Per Call (Please Call)">&lt;h3 style="margin:0;"&gt;Last Step, Please Call&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="number"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[international_ivr_number]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="instruction"&gt;from your phone in the next 10 minutes and follow the instructions. While on the call, you will be prompted to enter a PIN in order to complete the transaction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enter PIN [xxxx].&lt;/strong&gt;</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR Per Call (Follow Instructions)">&lt;strong&gt;If you do not complete this step within 10 minutes, this transaction will be cancelled.&lt;/strong&gt;</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR Per Minute (Please Call)">&lt;h3 style="margin:0;"&gt;Last Step, Please Call&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="number"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[international_ivr_number]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="instruction"&gt;from your phone in the next 10 minutes and follow the instructions. While on the call, you will be prompted to enter a PIN in order to complete the transaction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enter PIN [xxxx].&lt;/strong&gt;</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR Per Minute (Follow Instructions)">&lt;strong&gt;If you do not complete this step within 10 minutes, this transaction will be cancelled.&lt;/strong&gt;</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR Per Minute (Confirmation message)">Thank you for your purchase! You were billed a total of [$] for [product].</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR (Please Call)">&lt;h3 style="margin:0;"&gt;Last Step, Please Call&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="number"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[toll_free_number]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="instruction"&gt;from your home phone &lt;strong&gt;[home_phone]&lt;/strong&gt; in the next 10 minutes to complete the transaction.&lt;/span&gt;</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR (Follow Instructions)">Call [toll_free_number] NOW from your home phone and follow the instructions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you do not complete this step within 10 minutes, this transaction will be cancelled.&lt;/strong&gt;</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Private and secure payment">Private and secure payment</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="IVR Per Call (Time remaining to call)">Time remaining to call</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Invalid Zip Code">We're sorry, the Zip Code entered is invalid. The 5-Digit Zip Code can be found on the primary account holder's monthly phone statements.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Product Not Supported">Product/Price not available, please select from one of the following available products.</homelabel>
    <homelabel for="Products not available.">Products not available.</homelabel>
  </Home>
  <Mobile>
    <mobilelabel for="How it Works?">How it Works? US EN</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Select an item:">Select an item:</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Please enter your mobile number">Please enter your mobile number</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Completing Transaction">Completing Transaction</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Processing Order">Processing Order</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Sending PIN Code to your phone">Sending PIN Code to your phone</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Pay with your Mobile Phone">Pay with your Mobile Phone</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Continue">Continue</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Remember My Number">Remember My Number</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="A text message containing a PIN code was sent to your phone.">A text message containing a PIN code was sent to your phone</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Please Enter PIN Code">Please Enter PIN Code</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Transaction Cancelled.">Transaction Cancelled.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Sorry, there was a problem with your purchase.">Sorry, there was a problem with your purchase.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Purchase Confirmed">Purchase Confirmed</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Your purchase was successfully completed.">Your purchase was successfully completed.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Mobile Number">Mobile Number</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Done">Done</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Success, Please check your merchant website within 24 hours.">Your transaction was billed but there was a problem crediting your account. Please check your account later to verify delivery. If problem persists, please contact customer service.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Exceeded PIN number entry attempts">We're sorry, but your transaction cannot be completed because you have exceeded the number of PIN number entry attempts. For your security, your transaction has been cancelled. Please go back to the checkout page and try again.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Display Mobile Number">Mobile Number</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Legal Disclaimer">Charges go on your wireless account or phone bill. Msg&amp;Data rates may apply for wireless carriers. For customer support, please contact us at 1-888-408-0018 or email support@paymentone.com. By clicking *CONTINUE*, you are confirming that you are the account owner or have authorization from the account owner to make purchases. Supported U.S. mobile carriers: AT&amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon Wireless.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Verifying phone number.">Verifying phone number.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="MO Method">Send a text message (SMS) with the following code [xxxx] to [short_code]</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="MT Method">Send a text message (SMS) with the following code [xxxx] to [short_code]</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Private and secure payment">Private and secure payment</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Try Web Billing">Try Web Billing</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Time remaining to send SMS">Time remaining to send SMS</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Try again">Try again</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="MO/MT failure to iLEC">If you have a fixed line home phone number that you would like to use. Please [click_here] to continue.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Carrier Not Supported">We’re sorry, but your transaction could not be completed because your carrier or phone number is not currently supported.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Product Not Supported">Product/Price not available, please select from one of the following available products.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Operator ID Mismatch">Operator ID mismatch, please select from one of the following available products.</mobilelabel>
    <mobilelabel for="Products not available.">Products not available.</mobilelabel>
  </Mobile>
  <Anyphone>
    <anyphonelabel for="Pay with any phone">Pay with any phone</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Please enter your mobile or home number">Please enter your mobile or home number</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Phone number">Phone number</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Select a Method to Pay">Select a Method to Pay</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Pay With Your Home Phone">Pay With Your &lt;a id="openhome" class="openhome" style="cursor:pointer;" tabindex="2"&gt;Home Phone&lt;/a&gt;</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Pay With Your Mobile Phone">Pay With Your &lt;a id="openmobile" class="openmobile" style="cursor:pointer;" tabindex="4"&gt;Mobile Phone&lt;/a&gt;</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Error transaction could not be processed">Transaction could not be processed. Please try again.</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Error number not recognized">We're sorry, but your transaction could not be processed or your phone number was not recognized. Please try again.</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Remember My Number">Remember My Number</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="How it Works?">How it Works? US EN</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Continue">Continue</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Phone number verification">Phone number verification</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Private and secure payment">Private and secure payment</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Legal Disclaimer">Charges go on your wireless account or phone bill. Msg&amp;Data rates may apply for wireless carriers. For customer support, please contact us at 1-888-408-0018 or email support@paymentone.com. By clicking *CONTINUE*, you are confirming that you are the account owner or have authorization from the account owner to make purchases. Supported U.S. mobile carriers: AT&amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon Wireless.</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Select an item:">Select an item:</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Processing Order">Processing Order</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Product Not Supported">Product/Price not available, please select from one of the following available products.</anyphonelabel>
    <anyphonelabel for="Products not available.">Products not available.</anyphonelabel>
  </Anyphone>
</PaymentOne>
